Rehan Shivani

Watsonville, CA (831)266-5044 rehan.shivani@hotmail.com

Graduate in Computer application specializing in Cloud technology and Information security. with experience in deploying, maintaining, upgrading and repairing personal, workstation and server-grade computer systems. Skilled in Virtual machine creation and deployment on Cloud platforms including but not limited to Microsoft Azure, Amazon AWS as well as self hosted solutions.

Work Experience

IT Specialist

06/2017 to 08/2017 Materia Medica Richmond, CA

Temporary position as the company needed to setup and deploy a local network hosted on a server to operate machinery remotely as well and logging day to day activities and providing WiFi to employees.

Major Project - Parking System

01/2020 to 06/2020 University Project ADYPU

A Database management systems project using Java as a frontend to allot parking spots and log vehicles in a parking lot which got our group an A grade.

Source code linked below.

Final Major Project - Self hosted Sandbox server

01/2021 to 04/2021 University Project ADYPU

For my final project I recycled a personal computer with only 4 gigabytes of DDR2 memory to an ubuntu server which hosted multiple virtual machines using VirtualBox to host various types of server operations including SFTP for university wide cloud storage and a counterstrike server in an other instance which in turn allowed me to graduate with fair reviews.

Skills

Computer repair - 5 years

Computer software troubleshooting - 7 years

Computer assembly - 5 years

Server maintenance - 4 years

Server deployment - 4 years

Mobile phone/iPhone repair - 2 years

C++ - 3 years

C - 4 years

HTML - 4 years

CSS - 4 years

Java - 3 years

Microsoft Office - 7 years

Web development - 3 years

Penetration testing - 4 years

DBMS-MySQL - 3 years

DBMS-MongoDB - 2 years

Linux terminal scripting - 1 year

Linux-Bash - 2 years

Git - 3 years

Photoshop/AffinityPhoto - 3 years

Soldering - 2 years

Certifications / Licenses

IBM - Cybersecurity Fundamentals

07/2021

A foundational course on cybersecurity concepts, objectives, and practices. This includes cyber threat groups, types of attacks, social engineering, case studies, overall security strategies, cryptography, and common approaches that organizations take to prevent, detect, and respond to cyber attacks.

Education

Ajeenkya D.Y Patil University (ADYPU)

Bachelor's

Computer Applications Specializing in Cloud technology and Information security (CTIS)

Pune, India

08/2018 to 06/2021

RIMS International School

High school or equivalent Cambridge IGCSE Pune, India 07/2011 to 05/2014

Links

https://www.credly.com/badges/659b3bf2-22a7-4d4e-8ed3-6a80d54827b6?source=linked_in_profile

https://teriyakiboy98.github.io/WhoAmI/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rehan-shivani-70bb52179/

https://github.com/Teriyakiboy98/Java-Parking-System